Guide to the Charis Books and More and Charis Circle records, 1974-2015 RL.00214
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Charis Books and More and Charis Circle records
1974-2015 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Charis Books and More
RL.00214
37.5 Linear Feet
Charis Books and More, founded in 1974 in Atlanta, Ga., is the oldest feminist bookstore in the Southeast, and Charis Circle is a non-profit organization founded in July 1996 that furthers the mission of the bookstore by offering free educational and cultural events and programs to the community. Collection documents the day-to-day operation, programs, and mission of Charis Books and More and Charis Circle, and the interrelated nature of these two organizations. The financial records include those for Charis Books and More and Charis Circle. The ephemera include bookstore flyers and announcements, t-shirts, banners, framed posters, and book bags. There are also board minutes, log books, instructions, and reports for the bookstore, records for community programs (Sister Girls and Young Writers); poetry workshop materials for "Leaving Home, Becoming Home"; 2,500 photographs; and a DVD. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research; however, material related to sale of Charis Corporation is restricted for 30 years.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the Rare Book, Manuscript, and Special Collections Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Charis Books and More - Charis Circle Records were received by the Rare Book, Manuscript, and Special Collections Library as a purchase from 2005-2008, and as a gift in 2010 and 2015.
Historical Note
Charis Books and More, founded in 1974 in Atlanta, Ga., is the oldest feminist bookstore in the Southeast. Charis Circle is a non-profit organization founded in July 1996 that furthers the mission of the bookstore by offering free educational and cultural events and programs to the community.
Collection Overview
Collection documents the day-to-day operation, programs, and mission of Charis Books and More and Charis Circle, and the interrelated nature of these two organizations. The financial records include those for Charis Books and More (1983-2001) and Charis Circle (1996-2003). The ephemera (1976-2004) include bookstore flyers and announcements, t-shirts, banners, framed posters, and book bags. There are also board minutes (1983-1988 and 1997-1998); log books (1984-2001); instructions and reports for the bookstore; records for community programs (Sister Girls and Gaia Girls, 1999-2000); poetry workshop materials for "Leaving Home, Becoming Home"; 2,500 photographs and a DVD. There are also materials prepared for and at an event held at the Rare Book Room, 2005 Apr. 12: 10 file folders, approximately 12 items, including introductory materials and materials prepared by participants at the event. There are also administrative files and financial records, 1996-2005; clippings, 2004-2006; promotional material, 2004-2006; store log notebooks, 2003-2005; approximately 30 mounted photographs; correspondence, 2005-2006; zines; t-shirts. Also includes oversized material consisting of 17 posters; 1 collage mounted on wooden board; 3 posters with 30 mounted photographs; 10 laminated signs; 1 painted wooden sign. There are also administrative and programming materials for both Charis Books and More and the Charis Circle organization, many of which were created by Linda Bryant, a founding owner. Also includes newsletters, newspaper clippings, some posters, and a fabric banner. There are also two oversized foam-core posters from the Girls Speak Out/SisterGirls group based at Charis Books and More. There are also program fliers and planning materials for Charis Books and More as well as Charis Circle; also contains information about the Charis Board and its members, store log books and correspondence, some ephemera from the store's programming, news coverage, and fliers from other community events. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Posters; Newsletters; Ephemera; DVDs; Color photographs; Women's bookstores -- Georgia -- Atlanta; Women political activists -- United States; Women in the book industries and trade -- United States; Bookstores, etc.; Feminists -- United States; Bryant, Linda; Charis Books and More; Charis Circle
- Administrative Files Series, 1979-2008, 5 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Consists of materials that document the founding of Charis Books and More, Charis Circle, and the management of both organizations.
  Arrangement note
  Arranged in original order as received.
  - Bylaws, 1979-1986 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1997-2003 (Box 1)
  - Merchandising, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Speeches, 2002-2006 (Box 1)
  - Feminist Bookstore News, 1995-2000 (Box 1)
  - Feminist Bookstore Strategic Planning Conference, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Feminist Bookstore Network, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Professional literature, 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Professional development, 1994-2002 (Box 1)
  - Staff meetings, 1993-2002 (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Store management, 2002 and undated (Box 1)
  - American Bookseller's Association, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Charis Circle Board meeting minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 2)
  - Meeting minutes and bylaws, 2001-2006 (Box 2)
  - Sale of Charis Corporation (Box 2)
  - Personnel matters, undated (Box 2)
  - Board meeting minutes, 2004-2007 (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Administrative and planning materials, 2006-2008 (Box 2)
  - Meeting notes, undated (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1984-2006 (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Archives decision, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
  - Merchandising, 1984-2003 (Box 3)
  - Charis Circle Annual Report, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Charis Circle Board Meetings, 1997-2002 (Box 3)
  - Awards, 1997-2002 (Box 3)
  - Charis Circle Board Meetings, 1995-2003 (5 folders) (Box 4)
  - Charis Circle bylaws, mission statement, undated (Box 4)
  - Charis Circle mailing list, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Charis Circle strategic planning, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Board of directors meeting and notes, 2002-2005 (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Board of directors retreat, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Board of directors retreat, 2005 (Box 5)
  - Board of directors background materials, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Board member information and events, 2000-2002 (Box 5)
  - Strategic plan, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Strategic plan and Search conference, 2000-2001 (Box 5)
  - Strategic plan, 2005 (Box 5)
  - Related organizations, 2003-2005 (Box 5)
  - Charis Circle newsletters, 2000-2007 (Box 5)
  - Charis Circle information, 2007 (Box 5)
  - Board member profiles, 2003 (Box 5)
- Financial Records Series, 1977-2007 and undated, 8 boxes
  Contains the financial records for both Charis Books and More and Charis Circle. It includes budgets, ledger sheets, insurance information and financial statements.
  - Financial information, 1989-1993 (Box 6)
  - Insurance information, 1993-1994 (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Ledger sheets, 1987-1991 (Box 6)
  - Financial information, 1987-1991 (Box 6)
  - Financial information, 1989-1993 (Box 6)
  - Financial statements, 1993-1997 (Box 6)
  - Invoices, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
  - Budgets, taxes, business licenses, 1994-2001 (Box 7)
  - Grant applications, 1995-2000 (Box 7)
  - Insurance, 1984-1990 (Box 7)
  - Property maintenance, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Financial information, 1995-1998 (Box 7)
  - Ledger sheets, 1997-1999 (Box 7)
  - Financial information, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Ledger sheets, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Ledger sheets, 1998-1999 (4 folders) (Box 8)
  - Book orders, 1998-1999 (Box 8)
  - Financial information, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
  - Bank statements, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Financial information, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Charis Circle receipts, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Charis Circle bills and deposits, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Charis Circle financial information, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Charis Circle financial statements, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
  - Financial information, 1995-2001 (Box 9)
  - Property appraisals, 1997-2001 (Box 9)
  - Tax information, 1993-1999 (Box 9)
  - Bank statements, invoices, 1998 (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Bank statements, invoices, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Financial information, 1977-1996 (Box 9)
  - Accounts payable ledger, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Proposed sales agreement, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Financial information, 2001-2002 (Box 10)
  - Financial information, 2007 (Box 10)
  - Budget, 2002-2005 (Box 10)
  - Financial statements, 1991-1995 (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Financial information, 2000-2002 (Box 10)
  - Net worth report, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Ledger sheets, 1994-1998 (Box 11)
  - Ledger sheets, 1995-1998 (Box 12)
  - Financial management seminar, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Non-profit salary information, undated (Box 13)
  - Fund raising, 1996-1999 (Box 13)
  - Fund raising, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Development, 1995-1998 (Box 13)
  - Charis Circle fund raising 1995-2005 (Box 13)
  - Benefit auction, 1993 (Box 13)
  - Benefit auction, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Auction bids, undated (Box 13)
  - Fund raising event, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Fund raising displays, undated (Box 13)
- Store Operations Records, 1984-2005 and undated, 4 boxes
  These materials consist of store log books, calendars and other records documenting the daily operations of Charis Books and More.
  - Log books, 1984-1998 (Box 14)
  - Log books, 1998-2001 (Box 15)
  - Log books, 2001-2003 (Box 16)
  - Store calendars, 1999-2002 (4 folders) (Box 16)
  - Register instructions, 1987 and undated (Box 16)
  - Log books, 2003-2005 (Box 17)
- Publicity Series, 1979-2009 and undated, 6 boxes
  These materials consist of clippings of Charis in the news, Charis print advertisements, Charis Circle newsletters, catalogs, store publicity, and files of promotional materials from vendors.
  - Store publicity, 1996-2002 (Box 18)
  - Original art for publicity, undated (Box 18)
  - Book reviews, undated (Box 18)
  - Catalogs and fliers, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Book lists and catalogs, undated (Box 18)
  - Author publicity material, 2002 and undated (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Creative Loafing advertising rates, undated (Box 18)
  - Promotional materials, 2001-2007 (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Clippings, 1983-2006 (Box 19)
  - Clippings, 2005-2007 (3 folders) (Box 19)
  - Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 19)
  - Web site development, 2004 (Box 19)
  - Outreach opportunities, 2003-2004 (Box 19)
  - Book lists, 2004 (Box 19)
  - Publicity, 2005 (Box 20)
  - Book merchandising, 2005-2006 (Box 20)
  - Charis Circle newsletters, 2005-2007 (Box 20)
  - Magazine articles on Charis, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Print advertisements, 2005 (Box 20)
  - Email publicity printouts, 2007 (Box 20)
  - Book lists, 1995-2005 (Box 20)
  - Publicity and press releases, 2005-2007 (Box 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 (Box 20)
  - Publicity, 1997-2002 (contains audio CD) (Box 21)
  - Charis Circle newsletters, 1996-2000 (Box 21)
  - Store publicity, 1988-2004 (Box 21)
  - Clippings, 1979-1994 (Box 21)
  - Charis Circle brochure and fact sheets, 2002 (Box 21)
  - Feminist bookstore catalogs, 1993-1994 (Box 21)
  - Press releases, publicity, 1993-1996 (Box 21)
  - Bookstore and programming publicity, 1997-2000 (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - Vendor files, 1988-1994 (Box 22-23)
  - Web archives, 2012-2016
- Events and Programming, 1976-2007, 10 boxes
  Materials generated by community events produced by Charis Books and More and Charis Circle include fliers, press releases and author/artist information.
  - Charis birthday party fliers, 1976-1978 (Box 24)
  - Events, 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - Rhythm Fest, 1991 (Box 24)
  - Author and musician promotional materials, 1991-1993 (Box 24)
  - Events, 1991-1999 (Box 24)
  - 25th anniversary celebration, 1999 (Box 24)
  - Events, 2000-2002 (Box 24)
  - Word Weavers program, undated (Box 24)
  - Programming development, 1992-2002 (Box 24)
  - Program flyers, 1988-2003 (Box 25)
  - Event flyers, 1992-2001 (Box 25)
  - Event flyers, 1986-1991 (Box 25)
  - Program information, 1996-2004 (Box 25)
  - Program development materials, 1996-2000 (Box 25)
  - Events, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Program development and artist publicity, 2001-2002 (Box 26)
  - Programs, 2001 (Box 26)
  - Programming development, 2002 (Box 26)
  - Ongoing programs, 2003 (Box 26)
  - Programs, 2004 (Box 26)
  - 30th birthday celebration, 2004 (Box 26)
  - Display materials, undated (Box 26)
  - Program planning materials, 2003-2005 (3 folders) (Box 26)
  - Events, 2001 (Box 27)
  - Community events and flyers, 2004-2008 (Box 27)
  - Event DVDs, 2007: Anne Lamott, Audre Lorde and Midwifery presentation (Box 27)
  - Events, 2005 (2 folders) (Box 27)
  - Programming, 2002-2005 (Box 28)
  - Sister Girls and Gaia Girls programming, 1999-2000 (Box 28)
  - Sister Girls, 2003-2005 (Box 28)
  - Young Writer's Groups publicity displays, undated (Box 28)
  - High School Women Writers Group, 1999 (Box 28)
  - Sister Girls 'zines, 2002-2003 (Box 29)
  - Programming, 1988-1999 (Box 29)
  - High School Women Writers, 1998-2005 (4 folders), includes CD, Leaving Home, Becoming Home (Box 29)
  - Gaia Collective and 30th anniversary celebration, 2004 (Box 30)
  - SisterGirls, 2001-2006 (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - SisterGirls Zines, undated (Box 30)
  - SisterGirls Zines and feedback, 2003 (Box 30)
  - SisterGirls Camp, 2003 (Box 30)
  - Mentoring programs, 1999 and undated (Box 30)
  - SisterGirls journals, undated (Box 30)
  - SisterGirls, undated (Box 31)
  - Girls Speak Out/SisterGirls, 1997-2001 (Box 31)
  - SisterGirls, 2001-2002 (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Blackness for Sale, 2004? (Box 31)
  - Woman to woman violence, undated (Box 31)
  - Women in Print movement, 1997-1998 (Box 31)
  - Related community programming, 2004-2005 (Box 31)
  - Community programming, 2002-2004 (Box 32)
  - Community programming, 2002-2009 (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Community events and flyers, 2005 (Box 32)
  - Leading Younger Women, 2005 (Box 32)
  - Georgia Shares, 2002-2004 (Box 32)
  - Pride, 2002 (Box 32)
  - Atlanta LGBT activism, 2005-2006 (Box 32)
  - Sallie Bingham Center event, Leaving Home, Becoming Home, 2005 (Box 33)
- Realia and Oversized Items Series and undated, 1996-2008, 7 boxes
  - Charis T-shirts and tote bags, undated (Box 34)
  - Calendars, large format clippings, posters and graphic materials, 2004-2006 (Box 35)
  - Businesswomen of the Year plaque, 1990, and framed Atlanta Pride print, 1996 (Box 36)
  - Gender Talk event print, undated The Dinner Party Store print, undated, Be Present Inc. framed print, undated and The Charis Private Collection: Inspiring Images of Women Loving Women album, undated (Box 37)
  - Meeting notes, undated, Charis banner, undated, event posters, 2007-2008, mounted photographs, undated (Box 38)
  - Two oversized foam core posters from the SisterGirls program, undated (Box 39)
  - Charis Books/Charis Circle flag, undated (Box 40)
  - Wood-backed collage, undated (Box 47)
  - Wood-backed promotional material, undated (Box 48)
  - Posters and other promotional materials, undated (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous (Oversize-folder 1)
- Photographs Series, 1981-2007, 6 boxes
  Photographs document special events at Charis Books, including anniversary celebrations, and programming sponsored by Charis Circle. They include photos of Dorothy Allison, Gloria Anzaldua, Byllie Avery, Alison Bechdel, Charlotte Bunch, Phyllis Chesler, Kate Clinton, Alix Dobkin, Leslie Feinberg, Kay Hagan, bell hooks, Brenda Porter, Minnie Bruce Pratt, Amy Ray, Francine Reed, Emily Sailers, Gloria Steinem, and Alice Walker.
  Photos are arranged in loose chronological order, and in loose alphabetical order where dates are not provided. (Boxes 45-46)
  - Photograph album of (Box 41)
    - "Charis at 20" event featuring Alice Walker, 1994 (Box 41)
    - 25th anniversary event, 1999 (Box 41)
    - Charis events, 1981-1982 (Box 41)
    - Charis 10th birthday and building renovations, 1984 (Box 41)
  - box 42 (Box 42)
  - 1970s (Box 42)
  - 1980, 1983-1989, and undated (Box 42)
  - 1983-1992 and undated (Box 42)
  - Staff/Window Display Photos, 1983-2002, and undated (Box 42)
  - Events, 1984-2002 and undated (7 folders) (Box 42)
  - Events, Pauline Clance 1986? (Box 42)
  - Events (Box 43)
    - 1987, 1999 and undated (Box 43)
    - 1988 (includes negatives) (Box 43)
    - Tina Ansa, 1989 (Box 43)
    - 1989-1997 and undated (Box 43)
  - Sandra's Going Away Party, 1990s (Box 43)
  - 1990-2002, and undated (3 folders) (Box 43)
  - Negatives-SWMCF (Box 43)
  - Duplicates, 1991-1993, 2001, and undated (Box 43)
  - Events
    - Alice Walker, Variety Play House, 1992 (Box 43)
    - Events, 1993-2002 and undated (Box 43)
  - 1997-2002 (Box 44)
  - 1998 (Box 44)
  - Urban Nirvana, May 1998 (Box 44)
  - Events, Phyllis Chesler at Charis Books, May 15, 1998 (Box 44)
  - 1998-2002 (Box 44)
  - 1999 (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - 2000 (Box 44)
  - Children's Program with Brenda Porter, 2000 (Box 44)
  - First Celebration of Women in Music and Art, 2001 (includes negatives) (Box 44)
  - Negatives-Sister Girls Camp, 2001 (Box 44)
  - Stories, Pearl, Labyrinth, 2001 (Box 44)
  - Writing Retreat, 2001 (Box 44)
  - Sister Girls, 2001-2002 (Box 44)
  - Events, 2001-2002 (Box 44)
  - 2002 (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - ALCI Award, 2002 (includes negatives) (Box 44)
  - Charis Birthday, 2002 (Box 44)
  - Charis Concert, 2002 (Box 44)
  - Gaia Retreat, 2002 (Box 44)
  - Stories with Ulster and Others, 2002 (includes negatives) (Box 44)
  - Young Writers, 2002 (includes negatives) (Box 44)
  - Linda's Staff Party, July 2002 (Box 44)
  - Staff Events, 2002-2003 and undated (Box 44)
  - Events, 2002-2004 and undated (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - Children's Story Hour, Women's Sex Series, CeCe Caita, Shonia Brown, 2003 (Box 45)
  - Events, 2003 and undated (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Charis Circle Board Staff Retreat and Charis Books/Circle in Pride Parade, 2003 (Box 45)
  - High Tea and Conversation with Beverly Guy Sheftall and Johnette Cole, March 2003 (Box 45)
  - Alice Walker, April 27, 2004 (Box 45)
  - Events, 2004 (Box 45)
  - 2004-2007 (Box 45)
  - Dorothy Allison Tea negatives, undated (Box 45)
  - Author and Musician Promotional Photos, undated (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Alison Bechdel, undated (Box 45)
  - Black and White Events, undated (Box 45)
  - Charis Move (Old Store), undated (Box 45)
  - Events-Alix Dobkin and Dorothy Allison, undated (Box 45)
  - Events, undated (4 folders) (Box 46)
  - Negatives-Gaia Girls, undated (Box 46)
  - Events-bell hooks, undated (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Events-John Lewis, undated (Box 46)
  - Undated (5 folders) (Box 46)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 46)
  - Sister Girls and In-Store, undated (Box 46)
  - Barbara Smith, undated (Box 46)
  - Events-from Talking Bones, undated (Box 46)
- Accession (2015-0131), 1999-2015 and undated
  - Clippings, 2009 (Box 47)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 47)
  - Advertisement, 2009 (Box 47)
  - Girls Speaking Out Copyright, 2001 (Box 47)
  - Charis Circle promotional materials, 2000-2002 (Box 47)
  - Strategic planning initiative, 2000 (Box 47)
  - Bookmarks, undated (Box 47)
  - 25th anniversary, 1999 (Box 47)
  - Consent for photograph/video use, 2006 (Box 47)
  - Birthday celebration policy, undated (Box 47)
  - Charis Review, 2006-2008; 3 folders (Box 47-48)
  - Administrative, 2006-2008 (Box 48)
  - Meeting minutes, agenda, 2008 (Box 48)
  - Charis Circle log, 2007-2010; 4 folders (Box 48)
  - Bookmarks and business cards, undated (Box 49)
  - Programming pamphlets, 2009 (Box 49)
  - Charis Circle vision statement, 2009 (Box 49)
  - Southern Voice, 2006 (Box 49)
  - Atlanta Journal-Constitution, 2011 (Box 49)
  - 35th birthday, 2009 (Box 49)
  - Georgia Voice article, 2011 (Box 49)
  - Ms. Magazine, Fall 2009 (Box 49)
  - Atlanta Gay and Lesbian Chamber of Commerce Community and Business Directory, 2008 (Box 49)
  - Feminist Majority Foundation: Women of Color Conference, 2009 (Box 49)
  - Meeting notes and administrative papers, 2002-2009 (Box 49)
  - Volunteer information, 2009 (Box 50)
  - Intersex Writing, 2003 (Box 50)
  - Publicity and media information, 2006 (Box 50)
  - Charis Board Meeting Minutes and Financial Information, 2007-2009 (Box 50)
  - Disability Resource List (Box 50)
  - Disability Resource List-Braille (Box 50)
  - Intersex Resources (Box 50)
  - Event Calendar/Info (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 50)
  - Event Calendar/Info (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 51)
  - Charis Circle - Staff Reviews & Job Descriptions, 2008-2009 (Box 51)
  - Charis Circle Administrative Documents, 2001-2009 (Box 51)
  - Stories (Amanda Gable) (Box 51)
  - Womanwrites Anthology, 2002 (Box 51)
  - Assorted Charis Circle Photographs (Box 51)
  - Store Visitor Sign-In, 2002 (Box 52)
  - Summary Report, August 7, 2002 (Box 52)
  - Charis Circle Speech & Email, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Flyers and Promotional Materials, 2006-2009 (Box 52)
  - Fenuxe, November 2014 (Box 52)
  - Events and Galas, 2009 (Box 52)
  - Presbyterian Committee on the Self Help of People, June 16, 2011 (Box 52)
  - Partners, Sponsors, and Affiliates, 2005-2009 (Box 52)
  - Fourth Tuesday, October 2004 (Box 52)
  - Georgians for Choice, 2002-2003 (Box 52)
  - Emory Women's Center (Box 53)
  - ALCI (Box 53)
  - Sister Love, 2004 (Box 53)
  - Feminist Women's Health Center, 2002-2004 (Box 53)
  - Youth Pride, 2004 (Box 53)
  - Zami, September 28, 2002 (Box 53)
  - Global (Box 53)
  - Restaurant Events, 2004 (Box 53)
  - Sevananda, 2004 (Box 53)
  - Shay Youngblood, 2010 (Box 53)
  - Charis Circle Administrative Documents, 2000-2011 (Box 53)
  - Charis Circle Board of Directors, 2010-2011 (Box 53)
  - Kelley, 2001-2011 (Box 53)
  - Faith Communities (Box 53)
  - Volunteers Prospection (Box 54)
  - Author Events (Box 54)
  - Parking Lot, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Charis Circle Administrative Documents, 2007 (Box 55)
  - Charis Circle Publicity and Advertising (Box 55)
  - Assorted Charis Circle Photographs (Box 56)
  - Fundraising Materials (Box 56)
  - Emails to Add/Remove, 2008-2009 (Box 56)
  - October Fundraiser, 2007 (Box 57)
  - Program Calendars, November 2003-June 2015 (Box 57)
  - Paper Doll & 35th Anniversary Advertisement (Box 57)
  - Celebrating 35 Years Tote Bag (Box 57)
  - "A Memory, a Monologue, a Rant, and a Prayer" signed poster, September 26, 2007 (Box 57)
  - Charis Books & More Mailing List Sign Up Binder (Box 58)
  - Southern Voice - Local Life Article, September 8, 2006 (Box 58)
  - The Atlanta Journal-Constitution - City Life Article, December 22, 2005 (Box 58)
  - Southern Voice - Pride 2009, October 29, 2009 (Box 58)
  - Georgia Voice - Best of Atlanta Issue, July 24, 2015 (Box 58)
  - Georgia Voice - Holidy Gift Guide, November 21, 2014 (Box 58)
  - Georgia Voice - The Race to the Polls, October 24, 2014 (Box 58)
  - Southern Voice, September 8, 2006 (Box 58)
  - 4 VHS tapes: Bell Hooks, Alice Walker, Gloria Steinem, John Lewis speaking at Charis, 1991-1998 (Box 59)